Clement F. Haynsworth Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- United States Court of Appeals File, 1955-1989 (Box 6-201)
  - Case File, 1956-1989 (Box 7-159)
    - 1977 October term
      - Greubel v. Panama Canal Co., No. 77-2163
      - Wright v. United States, No. 77-2241
      - United States v. Moore, No. 77-2328
      - In re Webb, No. 77-2379
      - Steel Creek Community Ass'n v. United States Dep't of Transp., No. 77-2431
      - Stevens v. North Carolina, No. 77-8303
      - Edwards v. Garrison, No. 77-8305
      - Collingwood-on-the Potomac Citizens Ass'n v. Fish, No. 78-1182; (4 folders)
      - High Point Bank v. Poston, No. 78-1279
      - United States v. Wright, No. 78-5010
      - United States v. Humphrey, No. 78-5036
      - United States v. Truong Dinh Hung, No. 78-5046; (1 folder) (Box 52)
      - United States v. Truong Dinh Hung, No. 78-5123
      - Bowden v. Zahradnick, No. 78-6009
    - 1978 October term
      - Williams v. Leeke, No. 75-1936; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Fahrendholz, No. 76-1147
      - Hirschkop v. Snead, No. 76-2016; (3 folders)
      - Wham Constr. Co. v. United States, No. 76-2047
      - Eastern Band of Cherokee Indians v. North Carolina Wildlife Resources Comm'n, No. 76-2161
      - United States v. Newbourn, No. 76-2267; (1 folder) (Box 53)
      - Gathers v. County Council of Charleston, No. 76-2419
      - Hill v. Western Elec. Co., No. 76-2439; (3 folders)
      - Howard v. Aluminum Workers Int'l Union, No. 77-1046
      - Harris v. Winston, No. 77-1210
      - Jacobs v. Sibila, No. 77-1329
      - Hudspeth v. Figgins, No. 77-1442
      - United States v. Daniels, No. 77-1612
      - United States v. Neiswender, No. 77-1642
      - Rozen v. North Carolina Nat'l Bank, No. 77-1666 (Box 54)
      - Everly v. Califano, No. 77-1716
      - United States v. Moore, No. 77-1727
      - Elliott v. Califano, No. 77-1783
      - Brooks v. Califano, No. 77-1791
      - Kitchens v. Califano, No. 77-1798
      - Securities and Exch. Comm'n v. American Realty Trust, No. 77-1839
      - Venore Transp. Co. v. M/V Struma, No. 77-1935
      - Hoops v. Califano, No. 77-1939
      - Hizer v. Califano, No. 77-1948
      - Treadway v. Califano, No. 77-1994; (2 folders)
      - Jacobs v. Smith, No. 77-2013
      - United States v. Purnell, No. 77-2022
      - Barnette v. Califano, No. 77-2120
      - McLane v. Califano, No. 77-2122
      - Doran v. Alexander, No. 77-2137
      - Meade v. Bates and Rogers Constr. Corp., No. 77-2147
      - United States v. Richardson, No. 77-2184
      - Burgess v. Califano, No. 77-2202 (Box 55)
      - Buford v. Kistler, No. 77-2229
      - Jenkins v. Califano, No. 77-2259
      - Wesley v. Green, No. 77-2269
      - Edwards v. Sink, No. 77-2280
      - C. R. Cammer, Inc. v. United States, No. 77-2313
      - Simpson v. Hurst Performance, No. 77-2345
      - Hayes v. United States, No. 77-2347
      - Yolken v. United States, No. 77-2401
      - Triplett v. Califano, No. 77-2417
      - Wilson v. Commissioner, No. 77-2430
      - Hamiel v. Califano, No. 77-2434
      - Wade v. Animal Welfare League, No. 77-2446
      - Arlen Realty & Dev. Corp. v. Canada, No. 77-2447
      - Banking Center v. VNB Mortgage Corp., No. 77-2477
      - United States v. Mandel, No. 77-2487; (4 folders)
      - United States v. Horan, No. 77-2525 (Box 56)
      - Southers v. Wills, No. 77-2537
      - United States v. deBorja, No. 77-2553
      - Stephens v. United States Dep't of the Navy, No. 77-2621
      - Shifflett v. Califano, No. 78-1023
      - Howard v. Wilson, No. 78-1046
      - Hu v. Dees, No. 78-1049
      - Collins v. Califano, No. 78-1051
      - Ralston Purina Co. v. McFarland, No. 78-1055
      - Myers v. Bergland, No. 78-1058
      - Alice Ferguson Found. v. United States, No. 78-1099
      - Glueck v. McClaren, No. 78-1104
      - Bear Band Hosiery Co. v. Tights, Inc., No. 78-1116
      - Pfister v. Anderson Clinic, No. 78-1117
      - Harris v. Walker, No. 78-1133
      - Allied Towing Corp. v. Seaboard Coastline R.R., No. 78-1147
      - In re Capshaw, No. 78-1158
      - Cooper v. Metropolitan News Co., No. 78-1180
      - Schwaner v. Alexander, No. 78-1205
      - Bumgarder v. Keene Corp., No. 78-1247
      - Bast v. Federal Bureau of Investigation, No. 78-1260 (Box 57)
      - Hairston v. Irvin, No. 78-1273
      - Reichhold Chems. v. Federal Trade Comm'n, No. 78-1275
      - Grevas v. Somerset Navigation Co., No. 78-1295
      - Schaefer v. Hearst Corp., No. 78-1300
      - Davis v. Ampthill Rayon Workers, No. 78-1304
      - Davidson Supply Co. v. Federal Communications Comm'n, No. 78-1308
      - Lewis v. United States Lines, No. 78-1311
      - Morgan v. Hansbury, No. 78-1315
      - Vandergrift v. United States, No. 78-1407
      - Natural Area Council v. Adams, No. 78-1425
      - Nicosia v. Gray, No. 78-1429
      - In re Grand jury subpoena, May 1978, Baltimore, Md., No. 78-1507
      - Halco Eng'g v. United Elchem Indus., No. 78-1518
      - Southern Ry. v. United States, No. 78-1527
      - United States v. Inman, No. 78-1574
      - Van Sant v. United States, No. 78-1583
      - McCray v. Brown & Williamson Tobacco Co., No. 78-1585
      - Washington Metro. Area Transit Auth. v. Goldman, No. 78-1587
      - Morris v. McCaddin, No. 78-1592
      - Gamble Coals v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 78-1636
      - Brown v. Califano, No. 78-1684
      - Fracaro v. Priddy, No. 78-1687; (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 58)
      - Morgan and Co. v. Olin Corp., No. 78-1708
      - Jennings v. Edwards, No. 78-1713
      - Montgomery v. North Carolina Dep't of Motor Vehicles, No. 78-1741
      - Estate Life Ins. Co. v. Baird, No. 78-1746
      - In re Haughie, No. 78-1849
      - Thompson v. City of Burlington, No. 78-1850
      - United States v. Baker, No. 78-5011
      - United States v. Jones, No. 78-5026
      - United States v. Stroman, No. 78-5042
      - United States v. Jones, No. 78-5071
      - United States v. Williams, No. 78-5091
      - United States v. Johnson, No. 78-5092
      - United States v. Grenagle, No. 78-5096
      - United States v. Stevenson, No. 78-5100
      - United States v. Reason, No. 78-5104
      - United States v. Head, No. 78-5110
      - United States v. Williams, No. 78-5118 (Box 59)
      - United States v. Winstead, No. 78-5157
      - United States v. Keen, No. 78-5173
      - United States v. Herron, No. 78-5201
      - United States v. Sykes, No. 78-5204
      - United States v. Lawson, No. 78-5227
      - United States v. Webb, No. 78-5236
      - United States v. Smith, No. 78-6109
      - United States v. Bynum, No. 78-6117
      - Nasim v. Hubbard, No. 78-6155
      - Smith v. Leeke, No. 78-6159
      - McNeil v. Lally, No. 78-6161
      - Taylor v. Scism, No. 78-6195
      - Buckingham v. Maryland, No. 78-6263
      - Reeves v. Reed, No. 78-6278
      - Davis v. Zahradnick, No. 78-6311
      - Nasim v. Hubbard, No. 78-6389
      - Penn v. Johnson, No. 78-6413
      - Johnson v. Levine, No. 78-6416; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Dobson, No. 78-6428
      - United States v. Gibson, No. 78-6429
      - Williams v. United States, No. 78-6432
      - United States v. Swann, No. 78-6439
      - Richards v. McKenzie, No. 78-6474 (Box 60)
      - Ryman v. Fairfax Journal newspapers, No. 78-6528
      - Townes v. Mitchell, No. 78-6541; (2 folders)
      - Nasim v. Lally, No. 78-6577
      - Ligon v. Blankenship, No. 78-6587
      - Wilkins v. Maryland, No. 78-8080
      - Powell v. Califano, No. 78-8179
      - Pennington v. Whyte, No. 78-8317
      - Hogan v. Caudle, No. 78-8318
      - Rutherford v. Rudisill, No. 78-8319
      - Allard v. Petersam, No. 79-1055
      - United States v. Taylor, No. 79-1153
      - Wham v. United States Postal Serv., No. 79-1452
      - In re Scott, No. 79-1622
      - United States v. Stevens, No. 79-5064
      - Pierce v. Blalock, No. 79-6016
      - McGurgan v. Ford, No. 79-6174
      - Harrington v. Holshouser, No. 79-6254
      - McCloud v. Mahoney, No. 79-6402
      - Shaw v. Dixon, No. 79-6416
      - Braxton v. Reed, No. 79-6417
      - Easterling v. Williamson, No. 79-6445
      - Correll v. Reed, No. 79-6506
      - Wham v. Amis, No. 79-6509
      - Williams v. Mohn, No. 79-6558
      - Sayers v. McKenzie, No. 79-8084
    - 1979 October term
      - Stare v. Pearcy, No. 75-2331; (1 folder) (Box 61)
      - Napier v. Califano, No. 77-1609
      - International Union, United Auto. Workers v. American Standard, No. 77-1776
      - United States v. Ryan, No. 77-1960
      - United States v. Alexander, No. 77-2237
      - McCray v. Burrell, No. 77-2267
      - Ensminger v. Commissioner, No. 77-2302; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Lebedun, No. 77-2317
      - Ledford v. Delancey, No. 77-2457; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Gibson, No. 77-2574
      - Burdette v. Indiana & Mich. Elec. Co., No. 78-1031
      - Duke v. Califano, No. 78-1076
      - Phillips v. Califano, No. 78-1097
      - Smith v. Flax, No. 78-1201
      - University of Md. v. Cleland, No. 78-1211
      - Forte v. Massey, No. 78-1243 (Box 62)
      - Young v. Baltimore County Bd. of Educ., No. 78-1284
      - Hanchock v. Califano, No. 78-1289
      - Superior Bus Serv. v. United States, No. 78-1387; (2 folders)
      - Fleming v. Moore, No. 78-1389
      - City of Parkersburg v. Turner Constr. Co., No. 78-1397
      - Dick v. Califano, No. 78-1400
      - Cary v. RCo. Corp., No. 78-1442
      - Bevins v. Bevins, No. 78-1445
      - Penn v. Califano, No. 78-1509
      - Baltimore County v. Kreps, No. 78-1589
      - Eways v. Hammac, No. 78-1591
      - West v. Thomas, No. 78-1609
      - SAB Industri AB v. Bendix Corp., No. 78-1681
      - Klockner-Humboldt-Deutz v. Hewitt-Robins Div., No. 78-1703
      - In re Cedric's, Inc., No. 78-1732
      - Gardner v. Smith's Transfer Corp., No. 78-1747
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Indiana & Mich. Elec. Co., No. 78-1753
      - Reed's Jewelers v. United States, No. 78-1785 (Box 63)
      - Jizmejian v. Department of the Air Force, No. 78-1845
      - Hendrix v. Aetna Life Ins. Co., No. 78-1874
      - Boyd v. Califano, No. 78-1889
      - United States v. King, No. 78-5039
      - United States v. Hope, No. 78-5041
      - United States v. Pride, No. 78-5045
      - United States v. Shepherd, No. 78-5095
      - United States v. Myers, No. 78-5106
      - United States v. Johnson, No. 78-5164
      - United States v. Green, No. 78-5174
      - United States v. Johnson, No. 78-5206
      - United States v. Fon Lem Chin, No. 78-5243
      - United States v. McBride, No. 78-5244
      - Smith v. Morrissey, No. 78-6044
      - Everette v. Stephenson, No. 78-6059
      - Speed v. Maryland, No. 78-6228
      - Strader v. Garrison, No. 78-6235; (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - United States v. Boone, No. 78-6276
      - Wimbush v. Fuller, No. 78-6319
      - Withers v. Levine, No. 78-6336; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Widemon, No. 78-6463
      - Lambert v. Bordenkircher, No. 78-8135
      - Davis v. Young, No. 78-8149
      - Main v. Arlington County Circuit Court, No. 78-8178
      - Price v. Mitchell, No. 78-8347
      - Duvall v. Williams, No. 78-8406
      - Kendrick v. Edwards, No. 78-8499
      - Nestler v. Board of Law Examiners, No. 79-1002
      - Epps v. Califano, No. 79-1004
      - Federal Deposit Ins. Corp. v. American Bank Trust Shares, No. 79-1013
      - Vehicle Equip. Safety Comm'n v. National Highway Traffic Safety Admin., No. 79-1014
      - Lewis v. Finetex, Inc., No. 79-1019
      - Hopper v. Califano, No. 79-1020
      - Lockhart Power Co. v. Federal Energy Regulatory Comm'n, No. 79-1026; (2 folders) (Box 65)
      - DiAntonio v. Northampton-Accomack Memorial Hosp., No. 79-1039
      - Latham Park Manor v. Commissioner, No. 79-1058
      - J. T. Fritz & Sons v. Ironworkers' Local 16, Int'l Ass'n of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers, No. 79-1065
      - Williams v. Rector and Visitors of George Mason Univ., No. 79-1068
      - Simerly v. Sea-Land Serv., No. 79-1126
      - Morey v. Alexander, No. 79-1137
      - Lankford v. Law Enforcement Assistance Admin., No. 79-1158
      - North Carolina Nat'l Bank v. Gunter, No. 79-1197
      - Henningsen v. Dickerson, No. 79-1236
      - Haynsworth v. South Carolina Elec. and Gas Co., No. 79-1243
      - Granger v. Commissioner, No. 79-1245
      - Yoho v. Borg-Warner Corp., No. 79-1256
      - Cash v. Califano, No. 79-1279
      - In re Smith, No. 79-1327
      - Fortune v. Allied Maintenance Corp., No. 79-1344
      - Dossett v. Davis, No. 79-1363 (Box 66)
      - Ramsay Scarlett & Co. v. International Maritime Planning and Commercial Technology, No. 79-1364
      - Zabiegalski v. Greater Am. Constr., No. 79-1370
      - Brown v. Kinder, No. 79-1380
      - Daniels v. Califano, No. 79-1383
      - Federal Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Coast to Coast Invs., No. 79-1395
      - Heniford v. American Motor Sales Corp., No. 79-1430
      - Tracy v. Director, Memorial Hosp. Social Servs., No. 79-1445
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Burton Parsons & Co., No. 79-1463
      - Liberty Mut. Ins. Co. v. Colossus Maritime S.A., No. 79-1487
      - Master Printers of Am. v. Marshall, No. 79-1513
      - Wham v. United States Postal Serv., No. 79-1520
      - O'Hara v. Kovens, No. 79-1524
      - Federal Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Miller, No. 79-1554
      - Tatham v. Hoke, No. 79-1558
      - Taylor v. Zapata Haynie Corp., No. 79-1576
      - Flynn v. Harbor Baptist Church, No. 79-1597
      - Eigner v. Harris, No. 79-1601
      - Evans v. Central Piedmont Community College, No. 79-1618
      - Muller v. Commissioner, No. 79-1621
      - Yow v. American Home Assurance Co., No. 79-1648
      - Hyatt v. Harris, No. 79-1698
      - Jim Stacy Racing v. Roberts, No. 79-1722
      - Riddick v. Harris, No. 79-1728
      - Wham v. United States, No. 79-1745
      - Helm v. Virginia Elec. & Power Co., No. 79-1773
      - Wilson v. Harris, No. 79-1779
      - Sagner v. Coleman, No. 79-1780
      - Helm v. Various People, No. 79-1786
      - Moore v. Moore, No. 79-1822 (Box 67)
      - United States v. Wyatt, No. 79-5030
      - United States v. McCoy, No. 79-5046
      - United States v. Inglis, No. 79-5048
      - United States v. Breimeister, No. 79-5060
      - United States v. Moore, No. 79-5065
      - United States v. Knight, No. 79-5089
      - United States v. Harris, No. 79-5106
      - United States v. Williams, No. 79-5155
      - United States v. Allen, No. 79-5159
      - United States v. Baker, No. 79-5167
      - United States v. Henderson, No. 79-5235
      - United States v. Moore, No. 79-5257
      - United States v. Ray, No. 79-5258
      - United States v. Smith, No. 79-5279
      - United States v. Lemon, No. 79-5304
      - United States v. Copney, No. 79-5307
      - Harris v. Young, No. 79-6036
      - Sykes v. Johnson, No. 79-6056
      - United States v. Jeffers, No. 79-6096
      - United States v. McKethan, No. 79-6102
      - Williams v. Downes, No. 79-6117
      - United States v. Harrell, No. 79-6126
      - Watson v. Goodman, No. 79-6130 (Box 68)
      - Turner v. Purvis, No. 79-6151
      - Lopez v. Muncy, No. 79-6191
      - Mundy v. Director, Dep't of Corrections, No. 79-6197
      - Crews v. Bennett, No. 79-6220
      - Messer v. Jefferson, No. 79-6237
      - Lilly v. United States, No. 79-6260
      - Leach v. Bartram, No. 79-6276
      - Miller v. Hutto, No. 79-6297
      - Cox v. Johnson, No. 79-6299
      - Morris v. Cox, No. 79-6351
      - Jefferson v. Landon, No. 79-6352
      - Johnson v. Newport News Sheriff Dep't, No. 79-6372
      - United States v. Burton, No. 79-6405
      - Almond v. Cox, No. 79-6412
      - Davis v. Booker, No. 79-6419
      - Marsh v. Johnson, No. 79-6420
      - Mason v. Wolfe, No. 79-6427
      - Chestnut v. Keller, No. 79-6435
      - Lloyd v. Chief, United States Dist. Attorney, No. 79-6470
      - Graham v. Morris, No. 79-6482
      - Howerton v. United States Parole Bd., No. 79-6484
      - Wellons v. Brown, No. 79-6485
      - Wellons v. Baskerville, No. 79-6486
      - Bostic v. Edmisten, No. 79-6494
      - Reid v. Moore, No. 79-6499
      - Hofler v. Davis, No. 79-6503
      - Safrit v. Garrison, No. 79-6504
      - United States v. Alvarez-Pereira, No. 79-6519
      - Toliver v. Hester, No. 79-6534
      - Mundy v. Hutto, No. 79-6552
      - Lassiter v. Hunt, No. 79-6569
      - Wood v. Zahradnick, No. 79-6587
      - United States v. Gillis, No. 79-6591
      - Brown v. Harrison, No. 79-6595
      - Henley v. Palmer, No. 79-6608
      - United States v. Wickline, No. 79-6624
      - Silver v. Stephenson, No. 79-6651 (Box 69)
      - Phillips v. Mitchell, No. 79-6661
      - Graham v. Morris, No. 79-6664
      - Wellons v. Baskerville, No. 79-6669
      - Turner v. Young, No. 79-6670
      - Flanary v. Hall, No. 79-6683
      - Ross v. Kassa, No. 79-6719
      - Oakes v. Edwards, No. 79-6727
      - Harris v. Young, No. 79-6733
      - Vinson v. Holmes, No. 79-6734
      - Borders v. Reed, No. 79-6751
      - United States v. Kennedy, No. 79-6782
      - Griffin v. Garrison, No. 79-6783
      - Welch v. Lunger, No. 79-6789
      - Abrams v. North Carolina, No. 79-6798
      - Cooper v. Hinton, No. 79-6814
      - Riggs v. Gunnell, No. 79-6818
      - Campbell v. Fisher, No. 79-6837
      - Sloan v. Southampton Correctional Center, No. 79-6844
      - Eldridge v. Mitchell, No. 79-8058
      - Raines v. North Carolina, No. 79-8092
      - Crews v. Holmes, No. 79-8103
      - Brackett v. Hinton, No. 79-8104
      - Purvis v. Mitchell, No. 79-8111
      - Bostic v. Durham County Superior Court, No. 79-8112
      - Bowman v. North Carolina, No. 79-8116
      - Johnson v. Turner, No. 79-8122
      - Martin v. Hayes, No. 79-8141
      - Robinson v. Mitchell, No. 79-8193
      - Godfrey v. McCormick, No. 79-8273
      - Vickers v. Crooms, No. 79-8289
      - Carter v. Mitchell, No. 79-8290
      - Bryant v. Maryland, No. 79-8324
      - Smith v. Mitchell, No. 79-8365
      - Wellons v. Department of Correction, No. 79-8405
      - Hogan v. Holmes, No. 79-8416
      - Cross v. Mitchell, No. 79-8421
      - Williamson v. Muncy, No. 79-8422
      - Green v. Summers, No. 79-8429
      - Mallory v. Towley, No. 79-8453
      - Donithan v. Johnson, No. 79-8471
      - Hill v. Mitchell, No. 79-8479
      - Davenport v. Johnson, No. 79-8510
      - Nelson v. Mayhew, No. 80-1057
      - In re Pierce, No. 80-1091
      - Wicklund v. Harris, No. 80-1143
      - In re Freeman, No. 80-1226 (Box 70)
      - Minns v. Cabell, No. 80-1360
      - Cross v. Attorney Gen. of Va., No. 80-6020
      - Davenport v. Johnson, No. 80-6034
      - Luck v. Strickland, No. 80-6035
      - Graham v. Morris, No. 80-6040
      - Gardner v. Hewitt, No. 80-6087
      - Pless v. Pearce, No. 80-6088
      - United States v. McCormick, No. 80-6096
      - Sawyer v. Johnson, No. 80-6105
      - Thompson v. Whyte, No. 80-6124
      - Cox v. Harvey, No. 80-6127
      - Thompson v. White, No. 80-6131
      - Jackson v. Allbrook, No. 80-6141
      - Giles v. Sprinkle, No. 80-6154
      - Sykes v. Johnson, No. 80-6159
      - Sherrod v. Williams, No. 80-6161
      - Hinton v. Tilman, No. 80-6213
      - Grimes v. Walser, No. 80-6221
      - Hummer v. Hutto, No. 80-6222
      - Holley v. Purvis, No. 80-6224
      - Murphy v. Winston, No. 80-6231
      - Bostic v. Edwards, No. 80-6258
      - United States v. Harrell, No. 80-6275
      - Smallwood v. Blankenship, No. 80-6388
      - Toney v. Garrison, No. 80-6398
      - Kemper v. Ingram, No. 80-6422
      - Evans v. Stephenson, No. 80-6433
      - Hogge v. Cox, No. 80-6440
      - Joyner v. Superintendent, Powhatan Correctional Center, No. 80-6454
      - Robinson v. Cox, No. 80-6517
      - United States v. McCain, No. 80-6571
      - Flournoy v. Riddle, No. 80-6596
      - Cofield v. Mitchell, No. 80-8003
      - Richardson v. Allsbrook, No. 80-8006
      - Hudspeth v. Neff, No. 80-8014
      - Norwood v. Hinton, No. 80-8016
      - Johnson v. Mitchell, No. 80-8033
      - Coleman v. Johnson, No. 80-8047
      - Allen v. Garrison, No. 80-8059
      - Mines v. Sumner, No. 80-8061
      - McQueen v. Stephenson, No. 80-8079
      - Dillard v. Cox, No. 80-8083
      - Campbell v. Mitchell, No. 80-8097
      - Hudspeth v. Neff, No. 80-8112
      - Morgan v. Maryland, No. 80-8138
      - Bennett v. Marion, No. 80-8162
      - Bullard v. Allsbrook, No. 80-8178
      - Bartholomew v. Mitchell, No. 80-8211 (Box 71)
    - 1980 October term
      - Carroll v. Shepherd, No. 76-2391
      - Davis v. Davis, No. 77-1782; (2 folders)
      - Efthemes v. City of Wheeling, No. 78-1006
      - Richards v. Amoco Oil Co., No. 78-1654
      - United States v. Vaughan, No. 78-5072
      - United States v. Eades, No. 78-5216; (2 folders)
      - Jones v. Purvis, No. 78-6046
      - Newman v. Crews, No. 79-1070
      - Farnsworth Cannon v. Grimes, No. 79-1260; (1 folder) (Box 72)
      - Collins v. Califano, No. 79-1286
      - Huff v. Marine Tank Testing Corp., No. 79-1304
      - Fitzgerald v. Franklin Life Ins. Co., No. 79-1324
      - West Virginia v. Commissioner of Educ., No. 79-1338
      - Arlington Alliance, Ltd. v. General Servs. Admin., No. 79-1614
      - Robinson v. Ritchie, No. 79-1615
      - Harney v. Harris, No. 79-1639
      - Johnston v. Gilbert, No. 79-1644; (3 folders)
      - Gavin v. United States, No. 79-1727
      - West v. Ski Roundtop, No. 79-1778
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Union Boiler Co., No. 79-1855
      - Josefina Espino De Herrera v. Virginia Elec. and Power Co., No. 79-1859
      - Proctor & Schwartz, Inc. v. Rollins, No. 79-1876
      - Halco Eng'g v. Ferguson Enters., No. 79-1880 (Box 73)
      - United States v. Williams, No. 79-5074
      - United States v. Hemby, No. 79-5158
      - United States v. Jennings, No. 79-5254
      - United States v. Streets, No. 79-5328
      - Lee v. Downs, No. 79-6641
      - McNeil v. Panepento, No. 79-6724
      - United States v. Jones, No. 79-6749
      - Hamlin v. Warren, No. 79-6769; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Burnette, No. 79-6776
      - Bey v. United States, No. 79-6828
      - Thacker v. Stacy, No. 79-8077
      - Bougere v. Gross, No. 79-8253
      - Orpiano v. Parker, No. 79-8359
      - Huggins v. Brooks, No. 79-8499
      - Bermudez-Moreno v. Immigration and Naturalization Serv., No. 80-1001
      - Martin v. United States, No. 80-1003
      - Perkins v. Harris, No. 80-1045
      - Bocock v. Harris, No. 80-1061
      - Westmoreland Coal Co. v. Bowman, No. 80-1064 (Box 74)
      - Vandergrift v. United States, No. 80-1066
      - United States v. North Hampton Dev. Co., No. 80-1070
      - Keister Coal Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 80-1077
      - Rawlings v. Maryland, No. 80-1079
      - Farrel v. Furrow, No. 80-1119
      - Telephone Employees Credit Union v. Users, Inc., No. 80-1131
      - United Roasters v. Colgate-Palmolive Co., No. 80-1139; (2 folders)
      - King v. United States, No. 80-1145
      - St. Regis Paper Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 80-1148
      - Green v. Vectra Corp., No. 80-1159
      - Norton v. Shirley Contracting Corp., No. 80-1180
      - Benge v. Harris, No. 80-1215
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Sewell Plastics, No. 80-1224
      - Proctor & Gamble Mfg. Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 80-1275
      - Faulk v. Wyly, No. 80-1281
      - Powers v. Buchanan, No. 80-1294
      - Parkes v. Rice's Toyota World, No. 80-1295
      - Elby's Big Boy v. Boury, No. 80-1302 (Box 75)
      - Colonial Stores Div. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 80-1335
      - Beaman v. Barnwick, No. 80-1338
      - Smith v. G.F.C. Corp., No. 80-1349
      - Gilbert v. Unified Indus., No. 80-1362
      - Lane v. Secretary of the Army, No. 80-1395
      - Persuitte v. United States, No. 80-1398